Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2015
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Meridian Arts Ensemble members Tim Leopold, Benjamin Herrington, Raymond Stewart, Daniel Grabois, and Jon Nelson acknowledging applause after a performance at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0486.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_141.tif)
- Percussionists Bill Solomon, Matthew Gold, and Michael Lipsey performing Iannis Xenakis's Ohko on djembes at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-02, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0489.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_142.tif)
- Pianist Eric Huebner performing at a June in Buffalo 2015 seminar with composer Roger Reynolds (2nd from left in seats) in attendance, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0490.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_143.tif)
- Pianist Eric Huebner performing at a June in Buffalo 2015 seminar with composer Roger Reynolds (2nd from right, first row of seats) in attendance, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0493.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_144.tif)
- Pianist Eric Huebner performing at a June in Buffalo 2015 seminar with composer Roger Reynolds (2nd from right, first row of seats) in attendance, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0494.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_145.tif)
- Pianist Eric Huebner performing at a June in Buffalo 2015 seminar, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0498.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_146.tif)
- Pianist Eric Huebner speaking at a June in Buffalo 2015 seminar, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0499.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_147.tif)
- Pianist Eric Huebner performing at a June in Buffalo 2015 seminar with composer Roger Reynolds (far right, first row of seats) in attendance, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0500.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_148.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds (blue sweater) at a June in Buffalo 2015 seminar, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0501.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_149.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds (blue sweater) at a June in Buffalo 2015 seminar, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0504.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_150.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds (blue sweater) at a June in Buffalo 2015 seminar, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0505.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_151.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds (blue sweater) at a June in Buffalo 2015 seminar, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0507.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_152.tif)
- Pianist Eric Huebner listening to conversation at a June in Buffalo 2015 seminar with composer Roger Reynolds (2nd from left in seats), 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0509.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_153.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds in a seminar with student participants at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0510.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_154.tif)
- Pianist Eric Huebner at June in Buffalo 2015 seminar by Roger Reynolds with student participants, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0512.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_155.tif)
- Composer David Felder at control consoles with J. T. Rinker, Olivier Pasquet, and Patty Rihn in rehearsal of Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0513.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_156.tif)
- Composer David Felder at control consoles with J. T. Rinker, Olivier Pasquet, and Patty Rihn in rehearsal of Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0514.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_157.tif)
- Composer David Felder at control consoles with J. T. Rinker, Olivier Pasquet, and Patty Rihn in rehearsal of Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0517.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_158.tif)
- Composer David Felder at control consoles with J. T. Rinker, Olivier Pasquet, and Patty Rihn in rehearsal of Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0518.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_159.tif)
- Composer David Felder at control consoles with J. T. Rinker, Olivier Pasquet, and Patty Rihn in rehearsal of Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0519.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_160.tif)
- Composer David Felder at control consoles with J. T. Rinker, Olivier Pasquet, and Patty Rihn in rehearsal of Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0520.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_161.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman talking with trumpeter Mike Gurfield at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0521.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_162.tif)
- Trombonists William Lang and James Rogers looking at their parts during a rehearsal of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0523.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_163.tif)
- Composer David Felder at control consoles with J. T. Rinker, Olivier Pasquet, and Patty Rihn in rehearsal of Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0529.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_164.tif)
- Composer David Felder at control consoles with Phil Rehard, J. T. Rinker, Olivier Pasquet, and Patty Rihn in rehearsal of Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0531.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_165.tif)
- Trombonists William Lang, Benjamin Herrington, Jonathan Greenberg, and James Rogers during a rehearsal of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0538.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_166.tif)
- Composer David Felder at control consoles with J. T. Rinker and Olivier Pasquet in rehearsal of Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0541.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_167.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting a rehearsal of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with Ensemble Signal and the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0553.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_168.tif)
- Conductor Eduardo Leandro with composer James Chu and flutist Emi Ferguson at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0561.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_169.tif)
- Composer Roger Reynolds listening to a student in a seminar at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0571.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_170.tif)
- Conductor Eduardo Leandro and composer Timothy Page at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0580.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_171.tif)
- Conductor Eduardo Leandro in rehearsal with cellist Chris Finckel, clarinetist Jean Kopperud, flutist Emi Ferguson, and composer Timothy Page at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0582.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_172.tif)
- Pianist Stephen Gosling rehearsing with composer Stephen Yip at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0584.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_173.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting in a rehearsal of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with soprano Heather Buck, Ensemble Signal, and the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0592.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_174.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting a rehearsal of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0593.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_175.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting a rehearsal of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and the Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0594.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_176.tif)
- Conductor Eduardo Leandro looking at a score with composer Weijun Chen at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0599.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_177.tif)
- Eduardo Leandro conducting New York New Music Ensemble members Stephen Gosling, Curtis Macomber, Chris Finckel, Jean Kopperud, and Emi Ferguson in a performance at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0602.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_178.tif)
- Conductor Eduardo Leandro with New York New Music Ensemble members Stephen Gosling, Curtis Macomber, Chris Finckel, Jean Kopperud, and Emi Ferguson after a performance at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0603.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_179.tif)
- Pianist Stephen Gosling, violinist Curtis Macomber, and cellist Chris Finckel performing at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0605.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_180.tif)
- Pianist Stephen Gosling, violinist Curtis Macomber, and cellist Chris Finckel applauding a composer after a performance at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0606.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_181.tif)
- Eduardo Leandro conducting pianist Nicholas Emmanuel and New York New Music Ensemble members violinist Curtis Macomber, cellist Chris Finckel, percussionist Mike Truesdell, clarinetist Jean Kopperud, and flutist Emi Ferguson at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0607.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_182.tif)
- Eduardo Leandro conducting pianist Nicholas Emmanuel and New York New Music Ensemble members violinist Curtis Macomber, cellist Chris Finckel, percussionist Mike Truesdell, and flutist Emi Ferguson at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0608.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_183.tif)
- Eduardo Leandro conducting pianist Nicholas Emmanuel and New York New Music Ensemble members violinist Curtis Macomber, cellist Chris Finckel, percussionist Mike Truesdell, and flutist Emi Ferguson at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0610.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_184.tif)
- Conductor Eduardo Leandro and members of the New York New Music Ensemble, Stephen Gosling, Chris Finckel, Curtis Macomber, Mike Truesdell, Jean Kopperud, and Emi Ferguson at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0612.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_185.tif)
- Conductor Eduardo Leandro and members of the New York New Music Ensemble, Stephen Gosling, Chris Finckel, Curtis Macomber, Mike Truesdell, Jean Kopperud, and Emi Ferguson at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0613.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_186.tif)
- Conductor Daniel Bassin with cellist Veronica Nettles looking at the score of Augusta Read Thomas's Passion prayers at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0618.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_187.tif)
- Pianist Eric Huebner, violinist Mia Detwiler, cellist Jonathan Golove, and violist Yuki Numata Resnick rehearsing Steven Stucky's Piano quartet at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0620.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_188.tif)
- Pianist Eric Huebner, violinist Mia Detwiler, cellist Jonathan Golove, and violist Yuki Numata Resnick rehearsing Steven Stucky's Piano quartet at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0621.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_189.tif)
- Pianists Adam Sherkin and Anna Whistler at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0623.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_190.tif)
- Pianists Adam Sherkin and Anna Whistler performing Philip Glass's Four movements for two pianos at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0625.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_191.tif)
- Pianists Adam Sherkin and Anna Whistler performing Philip Glass's Four movements for two pianos at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Anna Whistler, Adam Sherkin piano Philip Glass Four Movements for Two Pianos ( 2008) Wednesday 4pm.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_192.tif)
- Pianists Adam Sherkin and Anna Whistler performing Philip Glass's Four movements for two pianos at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0627.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_193.tif)
- Pianists Adam Sherkin and Anna Whistler performing Philip Glass's Four movements for two pianos at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0628.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_194.tif)
- Pianists Adam Sherkin and Anna Whistler performing Philip Glass's Four movements for two pianos at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0629.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_195.tif)
- Pianists Adam Sherkin and Anna Whistler performing Philip Glass's Four movements for two pianos at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0631.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_196.tif)
- Pianists Adam Sherkin and Anna Whistler performing Philip Glass's Four movements for two pianos at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0632.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_197.tif)
- Pianists Adam Sherkin and Anna Whistler performing Philip Glass's Four movements for two pianos at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0633.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_198.tif)
- Pianists Adam Sherkin and Anna Whistler performing Philip Glass's Four movements for two pianos at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0634.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_199.tif)
- Pianists Adam Sherkin and Anna Whistler performing Philip Glass's Four movements for two pianos at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0637.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_200.tif)
- Pianist Eric Huebner, violinist Mia Detwiler, cellist Jonathan Golove, and violist Yuki Numata Resnick performing Steven Stucky's Piano quartet at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Mia Detwiller violin, Yuki Numata Resnick viola, Jonathan Golove cello, Eric Huebner Piano Piano Quartet (2005) by Steve~1.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_201.tif)
- Eric Huebner performing Roger Reynolds's Piano Etudes, Book 1 at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Eric Huebner PIANO ETUDES BOOK (2012) Roger Reynolds.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_202.tif)
- Eric Huebner acknowledging the composer after performing Roger Reynolds's Piano Etudes, Book 1 at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0643.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_203.tif)
- Composers Brian Ferneyhough and Roger Reynolds at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0646.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_204.tif)
- Pianist Eric Huebner with composers Roger Reynolds, David Felder, Brian Ferneyhough, and Steven Stucky at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0650.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_205.tif)
- Pianist Eric Huebner with composers Roger Reynolds, David Felder, Brian Ferneyhough, and Steven Stucky at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0651.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_206.tif)
- Pianist Eric Huebner with composers Roger Reynolds and Steven Stucky at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0652.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_207.tif)
- Pianist Eric Huebner with composers David Felder, Brian Ferneyhough, Roger Reynolds, and Harvey Sollberger at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0653.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_208.tif)
- Pianist Eric Huebner with composers Brian Ferneyhough, Roger Reynolds, and Harvey Sollberger at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-03, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0654.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_209.tif)